[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2004 the United States elected their _____ President.", "correct_answer": "43rd", "incorrect_answers": ["42nd", "30th", "40th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I ran outside but stopped dead due to my anthophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Flowers", "incorrect_answers": ["Pollen", "Paved roads", "Neighbors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Its a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World, Captain Culpepper finds the money and heads to Canada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Throughout this movie, Alonzo Mosely is constantly taking something from the other bounty hunter. What does he take from him all throughout the movie?", "correct_answer": "cigarettes", "incorrect_answers": ["advice", "his car keys away", "money"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the scientific term virga mean?", "correct_answer": "Rain that never hits Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["The effect on Mars that makes it appear as if water was on Mars", "The salt that remains after sea water has been desalinated", "Water that has undergone desalination"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the villains henchman in For Your Eyes Only, who brings a suitcase full of money at the swimming pool?", "correct_answer": "Emile Locque", "incorrect_answers": ["Teofilo  Diaz", "Giuseppe  Pugliese", "Joshua  Menasse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these are heterodonts?", "correct_answer": "Humans", "incorrect_answers": ["Snails", "Turtles", "Sharks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Switzerland is often associated with this product which is produced at the highest quality in the country.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Chocolate", "Watches", "Cheese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie is a bout Patrick Bateman, a wealthy investment banker who is trying desperately to hide his psychopathic alter ego from everyone.", "correct_answer": "American Psycho", "incorrect_answers": ["Wallstreet", "Henry: Portrait of a Serial Killer", "American History X"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the birthplace of Johann Strauss II, also known as The Waltz King?", "correct_answer": "Vienna", "incorrect_answers": ["Salzburg", "Berlin", "Prague"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fossil records have shown a species of giant penguin that once stood 4 feet high.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where can the Orange River be found ?", "correct_answer": "South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Turkey", "Canada", "South Asia"]}]